{
    "subject": "Guan_Hu",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Dirt__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Guan Hu created the film Dirt (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7752349972724915,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Guan Hu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5898886322975159,
            "question": "What year was the film Dirt released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5543405413627625,
            "question": "Is Guan Hu known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5451975464820862,
            "question": "Who directed the film Dirt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4777946472167969,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Guan Hu."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40366601943969727,
            "question": "What other films has Guan Hu directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3160834312438965,
            "question": "What genre is the film Dirt likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3104625344276428,
            "question": "Were there any awards associated with the film Dirt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2972729802131653,
            "question": "Is Guan Hu a well-known director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18983478844165802,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Dirt?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Guan Hu created the film Dirt (1994).",
            "html": "yago_17268_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Guan Hu a well-known director?",
            "html": "yago_17268_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any awards associated with the film Dirt?",
            "html": "yago_17268_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Dirt likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_17268_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17268_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information includes a document with the file path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17268/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt\" which contains the text \"'Indeed, Cow looks drastically different from Guan's 1994 debut, Dirt (Tou Fa Luan Le), a gloomy, subversive youth drama revolving around disillusioned underground rockers in Beijing.'\" This indicates that Guan Hu created the film \"Dirt\" (1994)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided in the documents states that \"Guan made his directorial debut with 1994 film \u201cDirt\u201d\" and provides details about the film, such as its cast and background. Therefore, it supports the statement that Guan Hu created the film Dirt (1994)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}